<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog RSS</title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:11:31 +0000</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[New Article on Medium - Active Reading with Children]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/active-reading-with-children/</link><description><![CDATA[Active Reading with Children
Update on Current Creative Projects

Lots of what most people would consider as their "Parenting Style" is subjective.  It's typically defined by how you and your spouse/co-parent were raised, the challenges and competencies of each of your children, and research.  Thankfully one thing most every parent on planet earth agrees with is that reading to your children is fundamental.

Taking the time each day to sit down with your little ones and read is truly priceless.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Creative Works In the... Works..]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/creativestuff/</link><description><![CDATA[Good Morning!

I hope this finds your inbox doing well.

I simply wanted to share a quick update for the subscribers of the GW blog.

As the holidays approach our thoughts naturally turn simultaneously to both reflection and planning.  We reflect on the past year, how we spent our time, the memories made, relationships developed, food eaten.  We plan for the coming year, what will we spend our time doing, what will be memorable a year from now, who shall we meet, what will we eat.  In that]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Google Ads Management is Back - With More Features, New Pricing, & New Strategies]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/google-ads-management-is-back-with-more-features-new-pricing-new-strategies/</link><description><![CDATA[AdWords Management is Back!
With More Ways To Target Your Next Client.

GhostWrite is very pleased to announce that we are once again taking on new Google Ads clients.  Back in May of this year, we stopped taking on new clients.  We started phasing this service out a few months prior, letting the few folks we had on our waiting list know that we weren't going to be able to accommodate them, during the months that would follow we continued to manage our core accounts while laying the foundation]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Project Spotlight - Save The Basilica (Asheville, NC)]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/basilica_project/</link><description><![CDATA[Save The Basilica!
A spotlight on a new project for GhostWrite.

I've always been quite a shutterbug.  Outside of my family, my favorite subject matter is either buildings or landscapes.  So when approached via our new Autumn Outreach Program to help the team over at the Asheville Design Center with a redux of their current fundraising site for the Basilica, I couldn't resist! 

If you haven't had an opportunity to tour the Basilica of Saint Lawrence, you should make it a point during your next]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Armchair SEO - The Simple DIY Guide To Great Content]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/armchair-seo/</link><description><![CDATA[Armchair SEO - Getting The Write Words Down

 
Whenever something goes wrong with one of our cars, depending on how complex, I initially attempt to fix it myself. Not to brag, I have a pretty good success rate using YouTube as a live repair manual.

The trade-off is, of course, my time. It could take hours to diagnose the real problem. I then have to locate repair instructions, determine if I have the correct tools, source the necessary parts or fluid, and then, finally, complete the task.

I'm]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Explanation of Patreon Subscriptions]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/explanation-of-patreon-subscriptions/</link><description><![CDATA[New Patreon Page Forthcoming]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Content or Copy? It's all about objective.]]></title><link>ghostwriteseo.com/blog/content-or-copy/</link><description><![CDATA[You've been tasked with giving your company website a facelift.  You and your designer have come to consensus when she hits you with it.

Do you have content for all these pages?

Well, do you?

Here's a better question to ask: What type of content do I need on these pages?

This question should elicit the purpose behind your website.  That purpose should then shape the content of the individual pages. But do you need simple content or do you need copy?  Better yet, what should you be looking]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
